cc.cc 2019-01-15

# CC.CC Call Forwarding

Keeping your personal information safe is one of our top priorities. CC.CC will use your personal information only for the purpose and within the scope to which you consent with the goal of providing CC.CC services (each a “Service” and, collectively, the “Services”) in a seamless manner. You may rest assured that CC.CC will never disclose your personal information to a third party unless otherwise required by the relevant laws and regulations or consented by you. We have developed this privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) applicable to all of the Services provided by CC.CC so that you may easily understand the way in which we protect your personal information and other related details. The Privacy Policy is open to the public at all times so you may read the full text of the Privacy Policy whenever you need to do so. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be notified to you to ensure that you understand the details of and reasons for such changes.

## Your personal information will be used by CC.CC to provide better services

CC.CC will collect your personal information as necessary to provide the Services in a seamless manner and to improve your user experience. In order to provide the basic features and other specialized functionalities of the Services pursuant to the Terms of Service for which your consent is given, it may be necessary for CC.CC to verify your identity information, age, account, contact information and device information. Your personal information may be used to search, register or notify other Service users who are in your contact list or who may be your CC.CC friends. Furthermore, your personal information may also be used to give any individual notifications, deal with any inquiries or disputes arising in connection with your use of the Services, send content for paid services, or process shipping and payment. In addition, your personal information may be used to perform statistical analysis for new customized services, provide event and advertising information, comply with obligations required under applicable laws and regulations, and prevent any improper use of your personal information that may cause harm to you in violation of law or the Terms of Service.

## CC.CC will collect the following information:

When you sign up for the Services or in the course of your use of the Services, CC.CC will collect your telephone number, contact information saved on your smartphone or other device (telephone numbers and names of third parties), username (nickname), CC.CC Account email address, For information about sending e-mail and password through the official website of CC.CC, individual applications or programs. You may choose to provide us with your birthday, gender, user ID, photos (including meta-information), and location information. Device-specific information (such as your operating system, screen size and unique device identifiers), IP address, cookies, date of visit, record of illegitimate use, service use records, etc. can be created automatically and collected in the course of service use or business process.

**CC.CC will also collect shipping information (including the name, mobile phone number and address) to ship your order. In addition to the above information, CC.CC may collect your credit card information, carrier information, gift certificate number or other information required for payment processing when you use paid services. Before you get started with an application or program, CC.CC will inform you of the personal information we collect to which you must consent in order to use the Service.**

## CC.CC will never disclose your personal information to a third party unless consented by you or otherwise required by law

CC.CC will use your personal information only for the purposes set forth above and will not disclose to or share your personal information with any third party unless consented by you in the course of your use of the Services or otherwise required by law. For any Services that are linked to a third-party service, CC.CC may provide your personal information to such third party with your consent within the scope necessary for your use of the Services.

## Your personal information will be discarded without delay after fulfilling the purpose of collection and use unless it is required to retain such information under the applicable laws or CC.CC’s internal policies.

After fulfilling the purpose of collection and use of your personal information to which you have consented, your personal information will be placed in a separate database (or a filing cabinet in case of paper records) and retained for a certain period of time stipulated under the applicable laws and regulations before being discarded. Paper records will be either shredded or incinerated, and electronic records will be discarded in an irreversible manner using technical methods. However, your email address (to send out emails regarding deleting your CC.CC Account and respond to user inquiries) and records pertaining to improper use of Services (to prevent any disputes arising from improper use of the Services) will be retained for a period of one year before being discarded in the manners as set forth above in accordance with CC.CC’s internal policies to prevent any disputes arising from improper use of the Services. Personal information retained by CC.CC as required by the applicable laws is as follows:

| 
* Information to be retained: Records on contracts and withdrawal of offers, etc. 
* Applicable laws: Act on the Consumer Protection in the Electronic Commerce Transactions, etc. 
* Term of retention: 5 years 

* * *

* Information to be retained: Records on payment and supply of goods, etc. 
* Applicable laws: Act on the Consumer Protection in the Electronic Commerce Transactions, etc. 
* Term of retention: 5 years 

* * *

* Information to be retained: Records on customer complaints and resolution of disputes 
* Applicable laws: Act on the Consumer Protection in the Electronic Commerce Transactions, etc. 
* Term of retention: 3 years 

* * *

* Information to be retained: Records on marks & advertisements 
* Applicable laws: Act on the Consumer Protection in the Electronic Commerce Transactions, etc. 
* Term of retention: 6 months 

* * *

* Information to be retained: Books and documentary evidence related to all transactions as prescribed by tax law 
* Applicable laws: Framework Act on National Taxes 
* Term of retention: 5 years 

* * *

* Information to be retained: Records on electronic financial transactions 
* Applicable laws: Electronic Financial Transaction Act 
* Term of retention: 5 years 

* * *

* Information to be retained: Records on Service visits 
* Applicable laws: Protection of Communications Secrets Act 
* Term of retention: 3 months   
---|---  
  
## CC.CC will protect your rights.

You (or your legal guardian if you are under 14 years of age) may review or change your personal information at any time, and you may also request to withdraw your consent to CC.CC’s collection and use of your personal information or to unregister from the Services. To be more specific, you may change your personal information by changing the relevant settings within the Services or unregister from the Services (or withdraw your consent) by simply clicking on “Unregister” in the Settings menu. You are also free to contact our personal information manager in writing, by phone or by email through our Customer Service Center for immediate action. Once you request to have your personal information corrected, we will not use or provide your personal information until it is corrected as requested.

## CC.CC may use cookies to provide the Services on personal computers.

In order to provide you with customized Services, CC.CC uses cookies, which are saved on your personal computer (“PC”) and retrieved whenever required for any PC-based Services. Cookies are small text files of information sent to your browser by the website operating server, which are then stored on the hard drive of your PC. When you visit a website, cookies are accessed by the server to ensure that your preferences are maintained, which helps you be more efficient. Moreover, cookies tell us how often your visit the website, how you use the website and what information interests you. In this way, we can provide the Services optimized for your needs. You have an option to enable or disable cookies. You may configure your browser to accept all cookies, get an alert before accepting cookies, or disable all cookies. Please bear in mind that you will not be able to access some of the Services requiring a login process if you disable cookies.

## CC.CC will protect your rights.

You (or your legal guardian if you are under 14 years of age) may review or change your personal information at any time, and you may also request to withdraw your consent to CC.CC’s collection and use of your personal information or to unregister from the Services. To be more specific, you may change your personal information by changing the relevant settings within the Services or unregister from the Services (or withdraw your consent) by simply clicking on “Unregister” in the Settings menu. You are also free to contact our personal information manager in writing, by phone or by email through our Customer Service Center for immediate action. Once you request to have your personal information corrected, we will not use or provide your personal information until it is corrected as requested.

## For any inquirie

If you have any questions, complaints or suggestions regarding the protection of personal information, please contact our Personal Information Protection Manager. We will use our best efforts to provide you with a timely and satisfactory response.

| 
* Name: Kil su Jong 
* Division: Security Part 
* Contact: [82-31-919-6171]   
---|---  
  
## Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be notified separately.

CC.CC may amend this Privacy Policy to, for example, reflect changes to the Services or applicable law. We will post a notice about any Privacy Policy changes, and the updated Privacy Policy will become effective 7 days from the day on which the notice is posted. However, if changes to our Privacy Policy materially affect your rights due to unavoidable reasons, we will give you a 30-day prior notice.
